<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>A Free And Open Source Real-Time Strategy Game on Warzone 2100</title><link>https://wz2100.net/</link><description>Recent content in A Free And Open Source Real-Time Strategy Game on Warzone 2100</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wz2100.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New website released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/new-website-released/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/new-website-released/</guid><description>Warzone 2100 now has a brand-new website, designed by @past-due.
Want to help?
Report Bugs in the Website Help us Translate the Website</description></item><item><title>Vulkan, DirectX, &amp; Metal support in-progress</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/vulkan-directx-metal-in-progress/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/vulkan-directx-metal-in-progress/</guid><description>Building on the great inital gfx_api and Vulkan work by @vlj, we&amp;rsquo;re now testing multiple new graphics backend support (slated for release in 3.4.0):
OpenGL ES 3.0 / 2.0 Vulkan 1.0+ DirectX (via LibANGLE) (on Windows) This is in addition to the existing support for:
OpenGL 3.0+ Core Profile (default), OpenGL 2.1 Compatibility Profile On macOS, Vulkan is supported via MoltenVK, which means Warzone2100 is capable of running on top of Metal now as well.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.3.0 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-3-3-0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-3-3-0/</guid><description>It has been three years since the last stable release. There is an enormous amount of changes in this release compared to 3.2.0. These changes include:
Display / UI scaling Performance improvements Major improvements to campaign The return of secondary orders removed in the previous release Fix for shooting through walls The return of macOS builds and many, many other things Below you can see the list of changes compared to the previous beta release.</description></item><item><title>Archived News</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/older-news/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/older-news/</guid><description>For archived releases and announcements, please see the News &amp;amp; announcements section of the forums.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://wz2100.net/privacypolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/privacypolicy/</guid><description>Your privacy is important to us. It is the Warzone 2100 Project&amp;rsquo;s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, https://wz2100.net, and other sites / services we operate.
What information do we collect? Personal information you disclose to us We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent.</description></item><item><title>Version Check</title><link>https://wz2100.net/versioncheck/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/versioncheck/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Webchat</title><link>https://wz2100.net/webchat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/webchat/</guid><description>If you want to arrange online games, or have a quick quesion to ask, you might want to use one of our chat options:
Like Discord? Join the official Warzone 2100 Discord server:
YOU&amp;#39;VE BEEN INVITED TO JOIN A SERVER Warzone 2100 Official Server Join Discord Benefits: Pick your nickname, view chat history, easily chat on mobile devices, (optionally) subscribe to receive announcements of new releases, voice chat, and more.</description></item></channel></rss>