<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>A Free And Open Source Real-Time Strategy Game on Warzone 2100</title><link>https://wz2100.net/</link><description>Recent content in A Free And Open Source Real-Time Strategy Game on Warzone 2100</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wz2100.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Version 4.1.1 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-1-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-1-1/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.1.1, a bug-fix release.
Including fixes for:
Respecting Hold &amp;amp; Fire At Will better Structure limits screen lighting Using faction models for UI buttons Chat cursor position Beta campaign balance tweaks Compilation / compatibility issues And a number of balance tweaks:
Make Heavy Plasma Launcher more useful with an &amp;ldquo;all rounder&amp;rdquo; role and reduce price of Plasma Cannon significantly (PR #2009) Tweak mortar research paths to decouple Bombard / Pepperpot from damage / ROF upgrades and Incendiary Mortar and reduce Pepperpot weight (PR #2021) Rebalance HVC and HVC Cyborg to have more ROF and 1 tile less range (PR #2022) Tweak accuracy and splash values on Sunburst and Cyclone anti-air weapons (PR #2032) View the full 4.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.1.0 - The Big Balance Update</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-1-0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-1-0/</guid><description>With 380 commits since the last release, it’s time for Warzone 2100 v4.1.0!
This release includes approximately 3 years of work on campaign balance &amp;amp; fixes (the &amp;ldquo;camBalance&amp;rdquo; mod), as well as numerous fixes for multiplayer balance.
Beware: &amp;ldquo;Insane&amp;rdquo; campaign difficulty should now be a challenge for even the most experienced of players. (New players should stick with a lower difficulty level.)
4.1.0 General Highlights: Merge of the &amp;ldquo;camBalance&amp;rdquo; mod that revamps campaign balance and fixes numerous issues Numerous multiplayer balance tweaks (see full changelog for details) Fix fog, add an option to toggle it on New design menu stats delta display Add a single player quit confirmation screen Allow building modules/derricks in a row (with drag &amp;amp; build) Add support for binding same keys to multiple actions in non-conflicting contexts Allow assigning key bindings to mouse keys Add &amp;ldquo;selection without group&amp;rdquo; hotkeys Move the whole group to the target location, not only the command droid New cheat makemehero makes selected units hero rank General improvements to Cobra AI / accounts for new balance changes Fix: Muzzle flash effects for Gauss, laser, and all kinds of weapons Fix: Several crash &amp;amp; UI soft-lock issues Fix: Various save-loading issues Fix: Do not handle RMB click while panning the camera Fix: Unclosable panels and flicker when using the Intelligence map and Design menus Fix: Heavy CPU usage on the Intelligence map Fix: VTOL collision with ground units Fix: Normalmapping of 3D models in menus / buttons Many other bug fixes View the full 4.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.1.0-beta1 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-1-0-beta1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-1-0-beta1/</guid><description>The first beta release of 4.1.0, 4.1.0-beta1, is available for testing! Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.1.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.1.0-beta1 from SourceForge Download 4.1.0-beta1 from GitHub Releases 4.1.0 beta1 Highlights: Fix fog, add an option to toggle it on Merge of the &amp;ldquo;camBalance&amp;rdquo; mod that revamps campaign balance and fixes numerous issues Numerous multiplayer balance tweaks (see full changelog for details) New design menu stats delta display Add a single player quit confirmation screen Allow building modules/derricks in a row (with drag &amp;amp; build) Add support for binding same keys to multiple actions in non-conflicting contexts Allow assigning key bindings to mouse keys Add &amp;ldquo;selection without group&amp;rdquo; hotkeys Move the whole group to the target location, not only the command droid New cheat makemehero makes selected units hero rank Fix: Several crash &amp;amp; UI soft-lock issues Fix: Various save-loading issues Fix: Do not handle RMB click while panning the camera Fix: Unclosable panels and flicker when using the Intelligence map and Design menus Many other bug fixes View the full 4.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.0.1 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-1/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.0.1, a bug-fix release.
Including fixes for:
Water rendering performance Additional Collective faction textures Broken map zoom cycle Autosave / saveload issues Multiplayer lobby issues Procedurally-generated map player positioning Compilation / compatibility issues ARM64 / Apple Silicon macOS builds Download Options
View the full 4.0.1 changelog
(For all the changes in 4.0.0, see the Version 4.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.0.0 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-0/</guid><description>With over 1000 commits since the last release, it’s time for Warzone 2100 v4.0.0!
4.0.0 General Highlights: New graphics backend support: New support for: Vulkan 1.0+ OpenGL ES 3.0 / 2.0 DirectX (via libANGLE, OpenGL ES -&amp;gt; DirectX) Metal (via MoltenVK, Vulkan -&amp;gt; Metal) In addition to the existing support for: OpenGL 3.0+ Core Profile (default), OpenGL 2.1 Compatibility Profile See the new &amp;ldquo;Graphics Backend&amp;rdquo; option in the Video Options menu.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.0.0-beta3 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-0-beta3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-0-beta3/</guid><description>The third beta release of 4.0.0, 4.0.0-beta3, is available for testing, with many bug fixes since beta1 &amp;amp; beta2. This is a very large release, and contains multiple changes. Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.0.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.0.0-beta3 from SourceForge Download 4.0.0-beta3 from GitHub Releases 4.0.0 General Highlights: New graphics backend support: New support for: Vulkan 1.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.0.0-beta2 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-0-beta2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-0-beta2/</guid><description>The second beta release of 4.0.0, 4.0.0-beta2, is available for testing, with many bug fixes since beta1. This is a very large release, and contains multiple changes. Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.0.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.0.0-beta2 from SourceForge Download 4.0.0-beta2 from GitHub Releases 4.0.0 General Highlights: New graphics backend support: New support for: Vulkan 1.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.0.0-beta1 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-0-beta1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-0-beta1/</guid><description>The first beta release of 4.0.0, 4.0.0-beta1, is available for testing! This is a very large release, and contains multiple changes. Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.0.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.0.0-beta1 from SourceForge Download 4.0.0-beta1 from GitHub Releases 4.0.0 beta1 Highlights: New graphics backend support: New support for: Vulkan 1.0+ OpenGL ES 3.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.4.1 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-3-4-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-3-4-1/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 3.4.1, a bug-fix release.
Including fixes for:
UI issues Keymap defaults Simple keybinds not firing when a meta key is held down Campaign bugs Compilation / compatibility issues Multiplayer lobby issues View the full 3.4.1 changelog
(For all the changes since 3.3.0, see the Version 3.4.0 release announcement.)
There have been over 70 commits since 3.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.4.0 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-3-4-0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-3-4-0/</guid><description>With over 485 commits since the last release, it&amp;rsquo;s time for 3.4.0!
3.4.0 Highlights: Graphics and UI improvements, including: fade effect when starting games, smoother mouse rotation, smoother zooming, interpolate frames in animation, occlude terrain ambiently Add: Frontend &amp;ldquo;continue last save&amp;rdquo; option Add: Quicksave feature Add: Autosave feature Add: Way to change most game settings with the in-game pause menu Add: Shortcut to quit to main-menu after victory Add: T4 technology level where all research is completed Add: Randomization of game options button in skirmish/multiplayer games Add: Add support for changing map, game name, and hosting player&amp;rsquo;s name after already hosting Add: Configuration of OpenAL-HRTF mode Add: In-game notification widgets Add: Keybinding configuration for camera pan Add: Discord rich presence / join support Add: Unit / kill count gui feature Add: BoneCrusher!</description></item><item><title>New website released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/new-website-released/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/new-website-released/</guid><description>Warzone 2100 now has a brand-new website, designed by @past-due.
Want to help?
Report Bugs in the Website Help us Translate the Website</description></item><item><title>Vulkan, DirectX, &amp; Metal support in-progress</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/vulkan-directx-metal-in-progress/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/vulkan-directx-metal-in-progress/</guid><description>Building on the great inital gfx_api and Vulkan work by @vlj, we&amp;rsquo;re now testing multiple new graphics backend support (slated for release in 3.4.0):
OpenGL ES 3.0 / 2.0 Vulkan 1.0+ DirectX (via LibANGLE) (on Windows) This is in addition to the existing support for:
OpenGL 3.0+ Core Profile (default), OpenGL 2.1 Compatibility Profile On macOS, Vulkan is supported via MoltenVK, which means Warzone2100 is capable of running on top of Metal now as well.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.3.0 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-3-3-0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-3-3-0/</guid><description>It has been three years since the last stable release. There is an enormous amount of changes in this release compared to 3.2.0. These changes include:
Display / UI scaling Performance improvements Major improvements to campaign The return of secondary orders removed in the previous release Fix for shooting through walls The return of macOS builds and many, many other things Below you can see the list of changes compared to the previous beta release.</description></item><item><title>Archived News</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/older-news/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/older-news/</guid><description>For archived releases and announcements, please see the News &amp;amp; announcements section of the forums.</description></item><item><title>License</title><link>https://wz2100.net/dist-license/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/dist-license/</guid><description>Warzone 2100 is distributed under the terms of the GPL:
GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 3, 29 June 2007
Copyright (C) 2007 Free Software Foundation, Inc. https://fsf.org/
Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute verbatim copies of this license document, but changing it is not allowed.
Preamble The GNU General Public License is a free, copyleft license for software and other kinds of works.
The licenses for most software and other practical works are designed to take away your freedom to share and change the works.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://wz2100.net/privacypolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/privacypolicy/</guid><description>Your privacy is important to us. It is the Warzone 2100 Project&amp;rsquo;s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, https://wz2100.net, and other sites / services we operate.
What information do we collect? Personal information you disclose to us We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent.</description></item><item><title>Support</title><link>https://wz2100.net/support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/support/</guid><description>There are many different options for getting help or support with Warzone 2100.
Documentation Try the in-game Tutorial to learn the basics Read the Quick Start Guide Help / Chat Ask for help via Discord / webchat Post in the forums Post in GitHub Discussions Reporting Bugs Please first search the existing Issues to make sure the bug hasn&amp;rsquo;t already been reported Report a new bug by opening a new Issue on GitHub</description></item><item><title>Version Check</title><link>https://wz2100.net/versioncheck/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/versioncheck/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Webchat</title><link>https://wz2100.net/webchat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/webchat/</guid><description>If you want to arrange online games, or have a quick question to ask, you might want to use one of our chat options:
Like Discord? Join the official Warzone 2100 Discord server:
YOU&amp;#39;VE BEEN INVITED TO JOIN A SERVER Warzone 2100 Official Server Join Discord Benefits: Pick your nickname, view chat history, easily chat on mobile devices, (optionally) subscribe to receive announcements of new releases, voice chat, and more.</description></item></channel></rss>