<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Notícias on Warzone 2100</title><link>https://wz2100.net/pt/news/</link><description>Recent content in Notícias on Warzone 2100</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wz2100.net/pt/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New Feature Spotlight: Replays</title><link>https://wz2100.net/pt/news/new-feature-replays/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/pt/news/new-feature-replays/</guid><description>Starting in Warzone 2100 version 4.2.0, replays are now available for skirmish and multiplayer games.
Every skirmish or multiplayer game is recorded to a (tiny) .wzrp file, which can be played back inside WZ.
For Skirmish replays: Go to &amp;ldquo;Single Player&amp;rdquo; &amp;gt; &amp;ldquo;View Skirmish Replay&amp;rdquo; For Multiplayer replays: Go to &amp;ldquo;Multi Player&amp;rdquo; &amp;gt; &amp;ldquo;View Replay&amp;rdquo; The files are stored in:
&amp;lt;configdir&amp;gt;/replay/skirmish &amp;lt;configdir&amp;gt;/replay/multiplay Note: Only the most recent few dozen replays are kept around automatically.</description></item><item><title>New Feature Spotlight: Spectators</title><link>https://wz2100.net/pt/news/new-feature-spectators/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/pt/news/new-feature-spectators/</guid><description>Starting in Warzone 2100 version 4.2.0, a brand-new option is available: spectators.
Spectators can: Watch a multiplayer game live* See the entire map Chat with other spectators (but not with players) Use the special specstats chat command to open a special statistics view Re-watch a locally-saved replay of the game later *Note: The game does not wait on spectators, once started, so if a spectator’s connection to the host is poor they may have a sub-par live viewing experience.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.0.0-beta3 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/pt/news/version-4-0-0-beta3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/pt/news/version-4-0-0-beta3/</guid><description>The third beta release of 4.0.0, 4.0.0-beta3, is available for testing, with many bug fixes since beta1 &amp;amp; beta2. This is a very large release, and contains multiple changes. Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.0.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.0.0-beta3 from SourceForge Download 4.0.0-beta3 from GitHub Releases 4.0.0 General Highlights: New graphics backend support: New support for: Vulkan 1.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.0.0-beta2 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/pt/news/version-4-0-0-beta2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/pt/news/version-4-0-0-beta2/</guid><description>The second beta release of 4.0.0, 4.0.0-beta2, is available for testing, with many bug fixes since beta1. This is a very large release, and contains multiple changes. Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.0.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.0.0-beta2 from SourceForge Download 4.0.0-beta2 from GitHub Releases 4.0.0 General Highlights: New graphics backend support: New support for: Vulkan 1.</description></item><item><title>Novo site lançado</title><link>https://wz2100.net/pt/news/novo-site-lan%C3%A7ado/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/pt/news/novo-site-lan%C3%A7ado/</guid><description>O Warzone 2100 tem agora um novo website, criado por @past-due.
Quer ajudar?
Reportar Bugs no Site Ajude-nos a traduzir o site</description></item><item><title>Suporte de Vulkan, DirectX &amp; Metal em progresso</title><link>https://wz2100.net/pt/news/vulkan-directx-metal-andamento/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/pt/news/vulkan-directx-metal-andamento/</guid><description>Tendo como base o excelente trabalho feito por @vlj para gfx_api e no Vulkan, estamos agora a testar o suporte backend para várias API gráficas (previsão de lançamento na versão 3.4.0):
OpenGL ES 3.0 / 2.0 Vulkan 1.0+ DirectX (via LibANGLE) (no Windows) Isto vem em adição ao support já existente para:
OpenGL 3.0+ Core Profile (default), OpenGL 2.1 Compatibility Profile No macOS, o Vulkan é suportado por Molten VK, o que significa que o Warzone2100 é agora capaz de correr com o Metal.</description></item><item><title>Versão 3.3.0 lançada</title><link>https://wz2100.net/pt/news/vers%C3%A3o-3-3-0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/pt/news/vers%C3%A3o-3-3-0/</guid><description>Já se passaram três anos desde o lançamento da última versão estável. Há uma quantidade enorme de mudanças neste lançamento se compararmos com a versão 3.2.0. Estas mudanças incluem:
Escala do display / interface do usuário ajustável Melhorias no desempenho Grandes melhorias na campanha O regresso das ordens secundárias removidas na versão anterior Um fix para os tiros através das paredes O regresso das compilações para macOS e muitas, muitas outras coisas Below you can see the list of changes compared to the previous beta release: View the full 3.</description></item><item><title>Notícias Arquivadas</title><link>https://wz2100.net/pt/news/not%C3%ADcias-antigas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/pt/news/not%C3%ADcias-antigas/</guid><description>Para lançamentos e anúncios arquivados, por favor veja a secção News &amp;amp; announcements do fórum.</description></item></channel></rss>