<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Un gioco di strategia in tempo reale gratuito e Open Source on Warzone 2100</title><link>https://wz2100.net/it/</link><description>Recent content in Un gioco di strategia in tempo reale gratuito e Open Source on Warzone 2100</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wz2100.net/it/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Version 4.5.0-beta1 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/it/news/version-4-5-0-beta1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/it/news/version-4-5-0-beta1/</guid><description>The first beta release of 4.5.0, 4.5.0-beta1, is available for testing! Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.5.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.5.0-beta1 from GitHub Releases Download 4.5.0-beta1 from SourceForge If you are on Linux, you can also get it on Flathub&amp;rsquo;s beta repo via:
flatpak remote-add --if-not-exists flathub-beta https://flathub.org/beta-repo/flathub-beta.flatpakrepo flatpak install flathub-beta net.wz2100.wz2100 And then to run: flatpak run --branch=beta net.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.4.2 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/it/news/version-4-4-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/it/news/version-4-4-2/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.4.2, a bug-fix and improvement release.
Including:
Numerous fixes for crashes, and Vulkan / OpenGL issues Fix: Clear active console messages when resuming from paused state Fix: Make sure VTOLs retreat to repair when attached to VTOL Strike/CB Fix: Move a spawn position on Gamma 3 Fix: Do not split departing player research centers with team in non-shared research mode View the full 4.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.4.1 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/it/news/version-4-4-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/it/news/version-4-4-1/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.4.1, a bug-fix and improvement release.
Including:
Numerous fixes for crashes, cleanup issues, and memory leaks Add: Chat Options UI, host mute / options Fix: Potential corrupt game config file issue Fix: Loading old maps with invalid map tile numbers Fix: Text input handling of virtual key codes, CTRL+V paste, and displaying virtual key names Fix: Always tell VTOLs to rearm after their VTOL Strike/CB sensor dies Fix: Spawn position of first clone in clone cheat Fix: Issues with OpenGL 3.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.4 - The Team, Terrain, &amp; Transparency Update</title><link>https://wz2100.net/it/news/version-4-4-0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/it/news/version-4-4-0/</guid><description>With almost 700 commits since the last release, it’s time for Warzone 2100 v4.4!
This release includes a brand-new &amp;ldquo;High Quality&amp;rdquo; terrain mode, an option to use &amp;ldquo;Classic&amp;rdquo; terrain, Group-management UI, &amp;ldquo;Quick Chat&amp;rdquo;, Team Strategy planning, options for handling player resources on leave in multiplayer, numerous graphics and performance improvements (on supported systems), and more!
With this release, the minimum requirements for running Warzone 2100 have changed to:
OpenGL 3.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.0.0-beta3 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/it/news/version-4-0-0-beta3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/it/news/version-4-0-0-beta3/</guid><description>The third beta release of 4.0.0, 4.0.0-beta3, is available for testing, with many bug fixes since beta1 &amp;amp; beta2. This is a very large release, and contains multiple changes. Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.0.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.0.0-beta3 from SourceForge Download 4.0.0-beta3 from GitHub Releases 4.0.0 General Highlights: New graphics backend support: New support for: Vulkan 1.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.0.0-beta2 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/it/news/version-4-0-0-beta2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/it/news/version-4-0-0-beta2/</guid><description>The second beta release of 4.0.0, 4.0.0-beta2, is available for testing, with many bug fixes since beta1. This is a very large release, and contains multiple changes. Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.0.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.0.0-beta2 from SourceForge Download 4.0.0-beta2 from GitHub Releases 4.0.0 General Highlights: New graphics backend support: New support for: Vulkan 1.</description></item><item><title>Nuovo sito pubblicato</title><link>https://wz2100.net/it/news/new-website-released/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/it/news/new-website-released/</guid><description>Warzone 2100 ha ora un nuovissimo sito Web, progettato da @past-due.
Vuoi aiutare?
Segnala bug nel sito web Aiutaci a tradurre il sito web</description></item><item><title>Version 3.3.0 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/it/news/version-3-3-0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/it/news/version-3-3-0/</guid><description>It has been three years since the last stable release. There is an enormous amount of changes in this release compared to 3.2.0. These changes include:
Display / UI scaling Performance improvements Major improvements to campaign The return of secondary orders removed in the previous release Fix for shooting through walls The return of macOS builds and many, many other things Below you can see the list of changes compared to the previous beta release: View the full 3.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wz2100.net/it/afterinstall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/it/afterinstall/</guid><description>The Warzone 2100 Project relies on donations from people like you to keep this great game running.
Money donated is used for:
Running costs such as hosting for multiplayer lobbies, autohoster, forums, and other infrastructure Continued maintenance and development Please Consider Donating In the interest of transparency, financial reports and transaction history are available publicly.
All donations are processed by Open Collective and the Open Source Collective (a registered 501(c)(6) non-profit in the United States).</description></item><item><title>Controllo Versione</title><link>https://wz2100.net/it/versioncheck/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/it/versioncheck/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Supporto</title><link>https://wz2100.net/it/support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/it/support/</guid><description>Ci sono diverse opzioni per ottenere aiuto o supporto con Warzone 2100.
Documentazione Prova l&amp;rsquo;esercitazione incorporata nel gioco per imparare le basi Leggi la guida rapida del gioco Aiuto / Chat Chiedi aiuto su Discord o tramite chat web Pubblica nei forum Pubblica nelle discussioni su GitHub Segnala i bug Prima cerca tra i problemi esistenti, in modo da essere sicuro che i problema non sia già stato segnalato Segnala un nuovo bug aprendo un nuovo problema su GitHub</description></item><item><title>Webchat</title><link>https://wz2100.net/it/webchat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/it/webchat/</guid><description>Se vuoi organizzare partite online o se hai una domanda veloce da chiedere, potresti usare una delle nostre chat:
Ti piace Discord? Unisciti al server Discord ufficiale Warzone 2100:
SEI STATO INVITATO A ENTRARE IN UN SERVER Warzone 2100 Server Ufficiale Entra Benefici Discord: Scegli il tuo soprannome, visualizza la cronologia della chat, chatta facilmente su dispositivi mobili, (facoltativo) iscriviti per ricevere annunci di nuove versioni, chat vocale e altro ancora.</description></item></channel></rss>