<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Un Joc de Strategie în Timp Real, Gratuit și cu Sursă Deschisă on Warzone 2100</title><link>https://wz2100.net/ro/</link><description>Recent content in Un Joc de Strategie în Timp Real, Gratuit și cu Sursă Deschisă on Warzone 2100</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wz2100.net/ro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New Feature Spotlight: Replays</title><link>https://wz2100.net/ro/news/new-feature-replays/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/ro/news/new-feature-replays/</guid><description>Starting in Warzone 2100 version 4.2.0, replays are now available for skirmish and multiplayer games.
Every skirmish or multiplayer game is recorded to a (tiny) .wzrp file, which can be played back inside WZ.
For Skirmish replays: Go to &amp;ldquo;Single Player&amp;rdquo; &amp;gt; &amp;ldquo;View Skirmish Replay&amp;rdquo; For Multiplayer replays: Go to &amp;ldquo;Multi Player&amp;rdquo; &amp;gt; &amp;ldquo;View Replay&amp;rdquo; The files are stored in:
&amp;lt;configdir&amp;gt;/replay/skirmish &amp;lt;configdir&amp;gt;/replay/multiplay Note: Only the most recent few dozen replays are kept around automatically.</description></item><item><title>New Feature Spotlight: Spectators</title><link>https://wz2100.net/ro/news/new-feature-spectators/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/ro/news/new-feature-spectators/</guid><description>Starting in Warzone 2100 version 4.2.0, a brand-new option is available: spectators.
Spectators can: Watch a multiplayer game live* See the entire map Chat with other spectators (but not with players) Use the special specstats chat command to open a special statistics view Re-watch a locally-saved replay of the game later *Note: The game does not wait on spectators, once started, so if a spectator’s connection to the host is poor they may have a sub-par live viewing experience.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.0.0-beta3 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/ro/news/version-4-0-0-beta3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/ro/news/version-4-0-0-beta3/</guid><description>The third beta release of 4.0.0, 4.0.0-beta3, is available for testing, with many bug fixes since beta1 &amp;amp; beta2. This is a very large release, and contains multiple changes. Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.0.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.0.0-beta3 from SourceForge Download 4.0.0-beta3 from GitHub Releases 4.0.0 General Highlights: New graphics backend support: New support for: Vulkan 1.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.0.0-beta2 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/ro/news/version-4-0-0-beta2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/ro/news/version-4-0-0-beta2/</guid><description>The second beta release of 4.0.0, 4.0.0-beta2, is available for testing, with many bug fixes since beta1. This is a very large release, and contains multiple changes. Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.0.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.0.0-beta2 from SourceForge Download 4.0.0-beta2 from GitHub Releases 4.0.0 General Highlights: New graphics backend support: New support for: Vulkan 1.</description></item><item><title>Noul site lansat</title><link>https://wz2100.net/ro/news/nou-site-lansat/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/ro/news/nou-site-lansat/</guid><description>Warzone 2100 are acum un site nou-nouț, proiectat de @past-due.
Doriți să ajutați?
Raportează Erori pe Site Ajută-ne să Traducem Site-ul web</description></item><item><title>Version 3.3.0 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/ro/news/version-3-3-0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/ro/news/version-3-3-0/</guid><description>It has been three years since the last stable release. There is an enormous amount of changes in this release compared to 3.2.0. These changes include:
Display / UI scaling Performance improvements Major improvements to campaign The return of secondary orders removed in the previous release Fix for shooting through walls The return of macOS builds and many, many other things Below you can see the list of changes compared to the previous beta release: View the full 3.</description></item><item><title>Știri Arhivate</title><link>https://wz2100.net/ro/news/stiri-vechi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/ro/news/stiri-vechi/</guid><description>Pentru versiuni arhivate şi anunţuri, vă rugăm să consultaţi secţiunea News &amp;amp; anunţuri a forumurilor.</description></item><item><title>Verificare versiune</title><link>https://wz2100.net/ro/versioncheck/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/ro/versioncheck/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Webchat</title><link>https://wz2100.net/ro/webchat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/ro/webchat/</guid><description>Dacă vrei să pregatești jocurile online sau să ai o întrebare rapidă, ai putea dori să folosești una dintre opțiunile noastre de chat:
Îți place Discord? Alătură-te serverului oficial de Discord Warzone 2100:
AI FOST INVITAT SĂ TE ALĂTURI UNUI SERVER Warzone 2100 Server Oficial Alătură-te Beneficii Discord: Alege porecla, vizualizează istoricul chat-ului, conversează ușor pe dispozitive mobile, abonează-te (opțional) pentru a primi anunțuri de noi lansări, chat vocal și multe altele.</description></item></channel></rss>