<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Un Juego de Estrategia en Tiempo Real Gratuito y de Código Abierto on Warzone 2100</title><link>https://wz2100.net/es/</link><description>Recent content in Un Juego de Estrategia en Tiempo Real Gratuito y de Código Abierto on Warzone 2100</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wz2100.net/es/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Version 3.4.1 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/es/news/version-3-4-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/es/news/version-3-4-1/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 3.4.1, a bug-fix release.
Including fixes for:
UI issues Keymap defaults Simple keybinds not firing when a meta key is held down Campaign bugs Compilation / compatibility issues Multiplayer lobby issues View the full 3.4.1 changelog
(For all the changes since 3.3.0, see the Version 3.4.0 release announcement.)
There have been over 70 commits since 3.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.4.0 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/es/news/version-3-4-0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/es/news/version-3-4-0/</guid><description>With over 485 commits since the last release, it&amp;rsquo;s time for 3.4.0!
3.4.0 Highlights: Graphics and UI improvements, including: fade effect when starting games, smoother mouse rotation, smoother zooming, interpolate frames in animation, occlude terrain ambiently Add: Frontend &amp;ldquo;continue last save&amp;rdquo; option Add: Quicksave feature Add: Autosave feature Add: Way to change most game settings with the in-game pause menu Add: Shortcut to quit to main-menu after victory Add: T4 technology level where all research is completed Add: Randomization of game options button in skirmish/multiplayer games Add: Add support for changing map, game name, and hosting player&amp;rsquo;s name after already hosting Add: Configuration of OpenAL-HRTF mode Add: In-game notification widgets Add: Keybinding configuration for camera pan Add: Discord rich presence / join support Add: Unit / kill count gui feature Add: BoneCrusher!</description></item><item><title>Nuevo sitio web lanzado</title><link>https://wz2100.net/es/news/nueva-web-lanzada/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/es/news/nueva-web-lanzada/</guid><description>Warzone 2100 tiene ahora un nuevo sitio web diseñado por @past-due.
¿Quieres ayudar?
Reportar Errores en el sitio web Ayúdanos a Traducir el Sitio Web</description></item><item><title>Vulkan, DirectX y Soporte de Metal en progreso</title><link>https://wz2100.net/es/news/vulkan-directx-metal-in-progress/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/es/news/vulkan-directx-metal-in-progress/</guid><description>Construyendo sobre el gran trabajo inicialgfx_api y Vulkan de @vlj, ahora estamos probando soporte para varios nuevos gráficos (programado para el lanzamiento en 3.4.0):
OpenGL ES 3.0 / 2.0 Vulkan 1.0+ DirectX (via LibANGLE) (en Windows) Esto es en adiciónalmente al apoyo existente para:
OpenGL 3.0+ Core Profile (default), OpenGL 2.1 Compatibility Profile En macOS, Vulkan es compatible a través de MoltenVK, lo cual significa que Warzone2100 es capaz de ejecutar encima de Metal ahora también.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.3.0 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/es/news/version-3-3-0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/es/news/version-3-3-0/</guid><description>It has been three years since the last stable release. There is an enormous amount of changes in this release compared to 3.2.0. These changes include:
Display / UI scaling Performance improvements Major improvements to campaign The return of secondary orders removed in the previous release Fix for shooting through walls The return of macOS builds and many, many other things Below you can see the list of changes compared to the previous beta release.</description></item><item><title>Noticias archivadas</title><link>https://wz2100.net/es/news/noticias-viejas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/es/news/noticias-viejas/</guid><description>Para publicaciones y anuncios archivados, por favor vea la sección Noticias y anuncios de los foros.</description></item><item><title>Chat web</title><link>https://wz2100.net/es/webchat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/es/webchat/</guid><description>Si quieres organizar juegos en línea, o tienes una pregunta rápida, tal vez quieras usar una de nuestras opciones de chat:
¿Te gusta Discord? Únete al servidor oficial de Discord de Warzone 2100:
HAS SIDO INVITADO A UNIRTE A UN SERVIDOR Warzone 2100 Servidor Oficial Unirse Beneficios de Discord: Elija su apodo, ver historial de chat, chatear fácilmente en dispositivos móviles, (opcionalmente) suscribirse para recibir anuncios de nuevas versiones, chat de voz y más.</description></item><item><title>Comprobar Versión</title><link>https://wz2100.net/es/versioncheck/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/es/versioncheck/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>