<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Un Juego de Estrategia en Tiempo Real Gratuito y de Código Abierto on Warzone 2100</title><link>https://wz2100.net/es/</link><description>Recent content in Un Juego de Estrategia en Tiempo Real Gratuito y de Código Abierto on Warzone 2100</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wz2100.net/es/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Version 4.0.0-beta3 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/es/news/version-4-0-0-beta3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/es/news/version-4-0-0-beta3/</guid><description>The third beta release of 4.0.0, 4.0.0-beta3, is available for testing, with many bug fixes since beta1 &amp;amp; beta2. This is a very large release, and contains multiple changes. Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.0.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.0.0-beta3 from SourceForge Download 4.0.0-beta3 from GitHub Releases 4.0.0 General Highlights: New graphics backend support: New support for: Vulkan 1.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.0.0-beta2 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/es/news/version-4-0-0-beta2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/es/news/version-4-0-0-beta2/</guid><description>The second beta release of 4.0.0, 4.0.0-beta2, is available for testing, with many bug fixes since beta1. This is a very large release, and contains multiple changes. Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.0.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.0.0-beta2 from SourceForge Download 4.0.0-beta2 from GitHub Releases 4.0.0 General Highlights: New graphics backend support: New support for: Vulkan 1.</description></item><item><title>Nuevo sitio web lanzado</title><link>https://wz2100.net/es/news/nueva-web-lanzada/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/es/news/nueva-web-lanzada/</guid><description>Warzone 2100 tiene ahora un nuevo sitio web diseñado por @past-due.
¿Quieres ayudar?
Reportar Errores en el sitio web Ayúdanos a Traducir el Sitio Web</description></item><item><title>Vulkan, DirectX y Soporte de Metal en progreso</title><link>https://wz2100.net/es/news/vulkan-directx-metal-in-progress/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/es/news/vulkan-directx-metal-in-progress/</guid><description>Construyendo sobre el gran trabajo inicialgfx_api y Vulkan de @vlj, ahora estamos probando soporte para varios nuevos gráficos (programado para el lanzamiento en 3.4.0):
OpenGL ES 3.0 / 2.0 Vulkan 1.0+ DirectX (via LibANGLE) (en Windows) Esto es en adiciónalmente al apoyo existente para:
OpenGL 3.0+ Core Profile (default), OpenGL 2.1 Compatibility Profile En macOS, Vulkan es compatible a través de MoltenVK, lo cual significa que Warzone2100 es capaz de ejecutar encima de Metal ahora también.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.3.0 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/es/news/version-3-3-0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/es/news/version-3-3-0/</guid><description>It has been three years since the last stable release. There is an enormous amount of changes in this release compared to 3.2.0. These changes include:
Display / UI scaling Performance improvements Major improvements to campaign The return of secondary orders removed in the previous release Fix for shooting through walls The return of macOS builds and many, many other things Below you can see the list of changes compared to the previous beta release: View the full 3.</description></item><item><title>Noticias archivadas</title><link>https://wz2100.net/es/news/noticias-viejas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/es/news/noticias-viejas/</guid><description>Para publicaciones y anuncios archivados, por favor vea la sección Noticias y anuncios de los foros.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wz2100.net/es/afterinstall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/es/afterinstall/</guid><description>The Warzone 2100 Project relies on donations from people like you to keep this great game running.
Money donated is used for:
Running costs such as hosting for multiplayer lobbies, autohoster, forums, and other infrastructure Continued maintenance and development Please Consider Donating In the interest of transparency, financial reports and transaction history are available publicly.
All donations are processed by Open Collective and the Open Source Collective (a registered 501(c)(6) non-profit in the United States).</description></item><item><title>Chat web</title><link>https://wz2100.net/es/webchat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/es/webchat/</guid><description>Si quieres organizar juegos en línea, o tienes una pregunta rápida, tal vez quieras usar una de nuestras opciones de chat:
¿Te gusta Discord? Únete al servidor oficial de Discord de Warzone 2100:
HAS SIDO INVITADO A UNIRTE A UN SERVIDOR Warzone 2100 Servidor Oficial Unirse Beneficios de Discord: Elija su apodo, ver historial de chat, chatear fácilmente en dispositivos móviles, (opcionalmente) suscribirse para recibir anuncios de nuevas versiones, chat de voz y más.</description></item><item><title>Comprobar Versión</title><link>https://wz2100.net/es/versioncheck/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/es/versioncheck/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>