<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ücretsiz ve Açık kaynak Gerçek Zamanlı Strateji Oyunu on Warzone 2100</title><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/</link><description>Recent content in Ücretsiz ve Açık kaynak Gerçek Zamanlı Strateji Oyunu on Warzone 2100</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wz2100.net/tr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Version 4.0.0-beta3 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/version-4-0-0-beta3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/version-4-0-0-beta3/</guid><description>The third beta release of 4.0.0, 4.0.0-beta3, is available for testing, with many bug fixes since beta1 &amp;amp; beta2. This is a very large release, and contains multiple changes. Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.0.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.0.0-beta3 from SourceForge Download 4.0.0-beta3 from GitHub Releases 4.0.0 General Highlights: New graphics backend support: New support for: Vulkan 1.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.0.0-beta2 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/version-4-0-0-beta2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/version-4-0-0-beta2/</guid><description>The second beta release of 4.0.0, 4.0.0-beta2, is available for testing, with many bug fixes since beta1. This is a very large release, and contains multiple changes. Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.0.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.0.0-beta2 from SourceForge Download 4.0.0-beta2 from GitHub Releases 4.0.0 General Highlights: New graphics backend support: New support for: Vulkan 1.</description></item><item><title>Yeni web sitesi yayınlandı</title><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/yeni-websitesi-yay%C4%B1nland%C4%B1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/yeni-websitesi-yay%C4%B1nland%C4%B1/</guid><description>Warzone 2100, @past-due tarafından dizayn edilmiş artık yepyeni web sitesine sahip.
Yardım etmek mi istiyorsun?
Web sitesinde bulunan hataları bildirin Bu web sitesini çevirmekte bize yardım edin</description></item><item><title>Version 3.3.0 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/version-3-3-0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/version-3-3-0/</guid><description>It has been three years since the last stable release. There is an enormous amount of changes in this release compared to 3.2.0. These changes include:
Display / UI scaling Performance improvements Major improvements to campaign The return of secondary orders removed in the previous release Fix for shooting through walls The return of macOS builds and many, many other things Below you can see the list of changes compared to the previous beta release: View the full 3.</description></item><item><title>Arşivlenmiş Haberler</title><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/daha-%C3%B6nceki-haberler/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/daha-%C3%B6nceki-haberler/</guid><description>Arşivlenmiş sürümler ve duyurular için lütfen forumda bulunan Haberler &amp;amp; Duyurular bağlantılarına tıklayın.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/afterinstall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/tr/afterinstall/</guid><description>The Warzone 2100 Project relies on donations from people like you to keep this great game running.
Money donated is used for:
Running costs such as hosting for multiplayer lobbies, autohoster, forums, and other infrastructure Continued maintenance and development Please Consider Donating In the interest of transparency, financial reports and transaction history are available publicly.
All donations are processed by Open Collective and the Open Source Collective (a registered 501(c)(6) non-profit in the United States).</description></item><item><title/><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/faq/general/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/tr/faq/general/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/faq/multiplayer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/tr/faq/multiplayer/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/faq/troubleshooting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/tr/faq/troubleshooting/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Sürüm Denetimi</title><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/versioncheck/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/tr/versioncheck/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Web sohbeti</title><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/webchat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/tr/webchat/</guid><description>Çevrimiçi oyun oluşturmak istiyorsanız veya sorularınız var ise, sohbet seçeneklerinden birini kullanın:
Mesela Discord? Resmi Warzone 2100 Discord sunucusuna katılın:
BİR SUNUCU KATILMAK İÇİN DAVET EDİLDİN Warzone 2100 Resmi Sunucu Katılın Discord avantajları: Nickname seçin, sohbet geçmişini görüntüleyin, mobil cihazlarınızdan kolayca erişin, (isteğe bağlı) duyuru, sesli sohbet, yeni sürümler ve dahası için abone olun.
Discord için kaydolun, sunucu üzerinden sohbet vs.</description></item></channel></rss>