<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ücretsiz ve Açık kaynak Gerçek Zamanlı Strateji Oyunu on Warzone 2100</title><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/</link><description>Recent content in Ücretsiz ve Açık kaynak Gerçek Zamanlı Strateji Oyunu on Warzone 2100</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wz2100.net/tr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Version 3.4.1 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/version-3-4-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/version-3-4-1/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 3.4.1, a bug-fix release.
Including fixes for:
UI issues Keymap defaults Simple keybinds not firing when a meta key is held down Campaign bugs Compilation / compatibility issues Multiplayer lobby issues View the full 3.4.1 changelog
(For all the changes since 3.3.0, see the Version 3.4.0 release announcement.)
There have been over 70 commits since 3.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.4.0 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/version-3-4-0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/version-3-4-0/</guid><description>With over 485 commits since the last release, it&amp;rsquo;s time for 3.4.0!
3.4.0 Highlights: Graphics and UI improvements, including: fade effect when starting games, smoother mouse rotation, smoother zooming, interpolate frames in animation, occlude terrain ambiently Add: Frontend &amp;ldquo;continue last save&amp;rdquo; option Add: Quicksave feature Add: Autosave feature Add: Way to change most game settings with the in-game pause menu Add: Shortcut to quit to main-menu after victory Add: T4 technology level where all research is completed Add: Randomization of game options button in skirmish/multiplayer games Add: Add support for changing map, game name, and hosting player&amp;rsquo;s name after already hosting Add: Configuration of OpenAL-HRTF mode Add: In-game notification widgets Add: Keybinding configuration for camera pan Add: Discord rich presence / join support Add: Unit / kill count gui feature Add: BoneCrusher!</description></item><item><title>Yeni web sitesi yayınlandı</title><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/yeni-websitesi-yay%C4%B1nland%C4%B1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/yeni-websitesi-yay%C4%B1nland%C4%B1/</guid><description>Warzone 2100, @past-due tarafından dizayn edilmiş artık yepyeni web sitesine sahip.
Yardım etmek mi istiyorsun?
Web sitesinde bulunan hataları bildirin Bu web sitesini çevirmekte bize yardım edin</description></item><item><title>Version 3.3.0 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/version-3-3-0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/version-3-3-0/</guid><description>It has been three years since the last stable release. There is an enormous amount of changes in this release compared to 3.2.0. These changes include:
Display / UI scaling Performance improvements Major improvements to campaign The return of secondary orders removed in the previous release Fix for shooting through walls The return of macOS builds and many, many other things Below you can see the list of changes compared to the previous beta release.</description></item><item><title>Arşivlenmiş Haberler</title><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/daha-%C3%B6nceki-haberler/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/tr/news/daha-%C3%B6nceki-haberler/</guid><description>Arşivlenmiş sürümler ve duyurular için lütfen forumda bulunan Haberler &amp;amp; Duyurular bağlantılarına tıklayın.</description></item><item><title>Sürüm Denetimi</title><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/versioncheck/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/tr/versioncheck/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Web sohbeti</title><link>https://wz2100.net/tr/webchat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/tr/webchat/</guid><description>Çevrimiçi oyun oluşturmak istiyorsanız veya sorularınız var ise, sohbet seçeneklerinden birini kullanın:
Mesela Discord? Resmi Warzone 2100 Discord sunucusuna katılın:
BİR SUNUCU KATILMAK İÇİN DAVET EDİLDİN Warzone 2100 Resmi Sunucu Katılın Discord avantajları: Nickname seçin, sohbet geçmişini görüntüleyin, mobil cihazlarınızdan kolayca erişin, (isteğe bağlı) duyuru, sesli sohbet, yeni sürümler ve dahası için abone olun.
Discord için kaydolun, sunucu üzerinden sohbet vs.</description></item></channel></rss>