<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Releases on Warzone 2100</title><link>https://wz2100.net/tags/releases/</link><description>Recent content in Releases on Warzone 2100</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wz2100.net/tags/releases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Version 4.5 - The Campaign Choices Update</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-5-0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-5-0/</guid><description>With over 800 commits since the last release, it’s time for Warzone 2100 v4.5!
This release includes a brand-new &amp;ldquo;Campaign Selector&amp;rdquo;, enhanced support for campaign mods, built-in &amp;ldquo;Classic Balance&amp;rdquo; campaign mod, numerous campaign &amp;ldquo;Tweak Options&amp;rdquo;, new included Addon Campaigns (Reclamation &amp;amp; Fractured Kingdom), an In-Game Guide, Formation Speed Limiting, Per-pixel Point Lighting, networking improvements, and more!
4.5 General Highlights: New Campaign Selector, enhanced support for campaign mods Added Balance Mod: &amp;ldquo;Classic Balance&amp;rdquo; Numerous &amp;ldquo;Tweak Options&amp;rdquo; to allow ultimate gameplay customizability &amp;ldquo;Timer Power Bonus&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Classic Timers&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;40 Unit Limit&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Autosaves-Only&amp;rdquo;, and more Addon Campaign: Reclamation A brand-new campaign from @DARwins1 with an original story taking place before the events of the main game: &amp;ldquo;Set out under the command of renowned General Edmund Clayde with the goal of laying the foundations of a new world.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.5.0-beta2 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-5-0-beta2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-5-0-beta2/</guid><description>The second beta release of 4.5.0, 4.5.0-beta2, is available for testing! Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.5.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.5.0-beta2 from GitHub Releases Download 4.5.0-beta2 from SourceForge If you are on Linux, you can also get it on Flathub&amp;rsquo;s beta repo via:
flatpak remote-add --if-not-exists flathub-beta https://flathub.org/beta-repo/flathub-beta.flatpakrepo flatpak install flathub-beta net.wz2100.wz2100 And then to run: flatpak run --branch=beta net.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.5.0-beta1 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-5-0-beta1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-5-0-beta1/</guid><description>The first beta release of 4.5.0, 4.5.0-beta1, is available for testing! Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.5.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.5.0-beta1 from GitHub Releases Download 4.5.0-beta1 from SourceForge If you are on Linux, you can also get it on Flathub&amp;rsquo;s beta repo via:
flatpak remote-add --if-not-exists flathub-beta https://flathub.org/beta-repo/flathub-beta.flatpakrepo flatpak install flathub-beta net.wz2100.wz2100 And then to run: flatpak run --branch=beta net.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.4.2 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-4-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-4-2/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.4.2, a bug-fix and improvement release.
Including:
Numerous fixes for crashes, and Vulkan / OpenGL issues Fix: Clear active console messages when resuming from paused state Fix: Make sure VTOLs retreat to repair when attached to VTOL Strike/CB Fix: Move a spawn position on Gamma 3 Fix: Do not split departing player research centers with team in non-shared research mode View the full 4.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.4.1 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-4-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-4-1/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.4.1, a bug-fix and improvement release.
Including:
Numerous fixes for crashes, cleanup issues, and memory leaks Add: Chat Options UI, host mute / options Fix: Potential corrupt game config file issue Fix: Loading old maps with invalid map tile numbers Fix: Text input handling of virtual key codes, CTRL+V paste, and displaying virtual key names Fix: Always tell VTOLs to rearm after their VTOL Strike/CB sensor dies Fix: Spawn position of first clone in clone cheat Fix: Issues with OpenGL 3.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.4 - The Team, Terrain, &amp; Transparency Update</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-4-0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-4-0/</guid><description>With almost 700 commits since the last release, it’s time for Warzone 2100 v4.4!
This release includes a brand-new &amp;ldquo;High Quality&amp;rdquo; terrain mode, an option to use &amp;ldquo;Classic&amp;rdquo; terrain, Group-management UI, &amp;ldquo;Quick Chat&amp;rdquo;, Team Strategy planning, options for handling player resources on leave in multiplayer, numerous graphics and performance improvements (on supported systems), and more!
With this release, the minimum requirements for running Warzone 2100 have changed to:
OpenGL 3.0+ (from: OpenGL 2.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.4.0-beta1 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-4-0-beta1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-4-0-beta1/</guid><description>The first beta release of 4.4.0, 4.4.0-beta1, is available for testing! Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.4.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.4.0-beta1 from GitHub Releases Download 4.4.0-beta1 from SourceForge If you are on Linux, you can also get it on Flathub&amp;rsquo;s beta repo via:
flatpak remote-add --if-not-exists flathub-beta https://flathub.org/beta-repo/flathub-beta.flatpakrepo flatpak install flathub-beta net.wz2100.wz2100 And then to run: flatpak run --branch=beta net.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.3.5 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-3-5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-3-5/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.3.5, a bug-fix and improvement release.
Including:
Add: Display kills and units in spectator stats UI Fix: &amp;ldquo;Get off my land&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;kill selected&amp;rdquo; cheats Fix: Don&amp;rsquo;t assign trucks from factories to commanders Fix: Repairs: Reset secondary only after &amp;ldquo;go-to-rally-point&amp;rdquo; was triggered Fix: Desync with losing player-turned-spectator when certain defensive structures remain Fix: Various potential crashes and corrupt config issues Add: /hostmsg lobby chat prefix that sends a message only to the host Change: Add Heavy Rocket Array to all skirmish AIs Change: Improvements to Nexus AI And a few multiplayer balance tweaks:</description></item><item><title>Version 4.3.4 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-3-4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-3-4/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.3.4, a bug-fix and improvement release.
Including:
Add: Separate Ban / Kick options in game lobby Add: Lobby command: /makeplayer Numerous fixes for crashes, cleanup issues, and memory leaks Fix: Let some older maps show up again in the map lists Fix: Always cancel research when starting it in another lab Fix: Missing sections on Tank Killer super cyborg Fix: Stop Mission Time and store it when the results screen pops up Change: Gamma 4: Remove middle tank traps guarding team Alpha and remove the repair units to account for new repair micro-AI Change: Always blow up walls and tank traps during Nexus transfers in campaign Change: Improve difficulty differences on Gamma 9 Change: Make Alpha 1-3 missions flow a bit more smoothly; Increase player flamer ranges Change: Make Gamma 1 easier by activating factories depending on what part of the valley you exit And some multiplayer balance tweaks:</description></item><item><title>Version 4.3.3 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-3-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-3-3/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.3.3, a bug-fix and improvement release.
Including:
Add: Cursor scaling support Numerous fixes for crashes, cleanup issues, and memory leaks Change: Make light / medium half-tracks a bit more visually distinct Change: Rebalance FastPlay to better fit the new campaign balance Change: Allow setting up to 20 research labs in the limits menu Fix: Don&amp;rsquo;t override orders with guard behavior when done repairing, unless explicitly ordered to repair Fix: [Audio] Improve stream buffer exhaustion handling to better avoid occasional music resets Fix: Load structure and droid limits before loading droids and structures Fix: Default initialize the NP artifact group waypoint on Alpha 11 so grabbing the artifact first won&amp;rsquo;t interfere with their movement Fix: Fix config file not storing the correct color variable when selecting a flag color in the options menu, thus reverting to green after level exit Fix: Do not play attacked sounds from friendly fire And a few multiplayer balance tweaks:</description></item><item><title>Version 4.3.2 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-3-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-3-2/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.3.2, a bug-fix and improvement release.
Including:
Numerous fixes for crashes, cleanup issues, and memory leaks Fix: Restoring window sometimes shows black screen in OpenGL mode Fix: Possible high CPU usage when minimizing window in Vulkan mode Fix: Default fullscreen dimensions should match the current resolution Fix: PNG files should take precedence over KTX2 files, to support mods Fix: Missing top section on cyborg repair turret Fix: Update generic design tank And a few multiplayer balance tweaks:</description></item><item><title>Version 4.3 - The Easy Update</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-3-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-3-1/</guid><description>With over 630 commits since the last release, it’s time for Warzone 2100 v4.3!
This release includes a new &amp;ldquo;Super Easy&amp;rdquo; campaign difficulty mode, texture compression support, an additional new &amp;ldquo;Aftermath&amp;rdquo; soundtrack from Lupus-Mechanicus, model and rendering improvements and fixes, countless bug fixes, and more!
Version 4.3.1 is the first official stable release in the 4.3.x series.
4.3 General Highlights: New &amp;ldquo;Super Easy&amp;rdquo; difficulty for campaign Additional new &amp;ldquo;Aftermath&amp;rdquo; soundtrack (from Lupus-Mechanicus) Add &amp;ldquo;LOD Distance&amp;rdquo; Graphics option, to adjust texture sharpness at distance (defaults to &amp;ldquo;High&amp;rdquo;) Add new Video Options (&amp;ldquo;Minimize on Focus Loss&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Alt+Enter Toggle&amp;rdquo;) Add Flatpak builds (for Linux) Support for bidirectional text using fribidi Improve Cobra AI yet again (balances against defensive / system research when 1v1 on high oil maps) Show the rank a unit will have if it were produced next Add console message when limits change Update campaign balance (and fixes) for: Alpha 2, Alpha 6, later Beta missions, Beta-end, Gamma 2 Fix: Chinese, Japanese, Korean text display Fix: Rendering improvements for text and translucent effects Fix: Inaccurate calculations on lower-performance systems affecting placing blueprints, rotation of camera, etc Fix: Returned and redesigned classic models for wheeled propulsion, light and medium half-tracks Fix: Model errors with the: cyclone flak, scavenger cranes, wrecked tanker, water pipe features, howitzer, mortar models, retribution body + hover propulsion, VTOL assault gun, tank factory Fix: Cyborg and Super Cyborg shadow issues Fix: Improve a bottleneck in shadow calculations Fix: Make artillery fire over walls Fix: Direct weapon: Don&amp;rsquo;t fire when blocked by defense hardpoint Fix: Simplify repairs logic, prevent &amp;ldquo;stuck&amp;rdquo; repair stations Fix: Hotkey doesn&amp;rsquo;t count selected units correctly Fix: Do not form alliances with scavengers when starting games Fix: Chat message is sent upon clicking anywhere outside of chat widget Fix: Fix the balance of FastPlay since the merging of camBalance Fix: When starting Beta / Gamma from the main menu, no longer block extra structure space at the LZ Fix: Fix OpenGL antialiasing only working at 2x Fix: Vulkan device selection when CPU device types (like llvmpipe) are present Fix: Fix longstanding save-related issue where incomplete research topics could disappear Fix: Build status for trucks in helping mode Fix: Redundant components becoming available Fix: Keep aspect ratio for sequences in full screen Fix: Make Blender .</description></item><item><title>Version 4.3.0-beta3 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-3-0-beta3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-3-0-beta3/</guid><description>The latest beta release of 4.3.0, 4.3.0-beta3, is available for testing! Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.3.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.3.0-beta3 from GitHub Releases Download 4.3.0-beta3 from SourceForge 4.3.0 beta 3 Highlights: Add: &amp;ldquo;LOD Distance&amp;rdquo; Graphics option, to adjust texture sharpness at distance (set default to &amp;ldquo;High&amp;rdquo;) Fix: Nickname selection in lobby Fix: Cancel RTR when fully repaired, and there are no repair stations Fix: Build status for trucks in helping mode Fix: Keep aspect ratio for sequences in full screen Fix: Returned and redesigned classic models for wheeled propulsion, light and medium half-tracks Fix: Model errors with the: retribution body + hover propulsion, VTOL assault gun, tank factory And many crash fixes Overall 4.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.3.0-beta2 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-3-0-beta2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-3-0-beta2/</guid><description>The latest beta release of 4.3.0, 4.3.0-beta2, is available for testing! Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.3.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.3.0-beta2 from GitHub Releases Download 4.3.0-beta2 from SourceForge 4.3.0 beta Highlights: New &amp;ldquo;Super Easy&amp;rdquo; difficulty for campaign Additional new &amp;ldquo;Aftermath&amp;rdquo; soundtrack (from Lupus-Mechanicus) Add Flatpak builds (for Linux) Support for bidirectional text using fribidi Improve Cobra AI yet again (balances against defensive / system research when 1v1 on high oil maps) Show the rank a unit will have if it were produced next Add console message when limits change Update campaign balance (and fixes) for: Alpha 2, Alpha 6, later Beta missions, Beta-end, Gamma 2 Fix: Chinese, Japanese, Korean text display Fix: Rendering improvements for text and translucent effects Fix: Inaccurate calculations on lower-performance systems affecting placing blueprints, rotation of camera, etc Fix: Model errors with the: cyclone flak, scavenger cranes, wrecked tanker, water pipe features, howitzer, mortar models Fix: Cyborg and Super Cyborg shadow issues Fix: Improve a bottleneck in shadow calculations Fix: Make artillery fire over walls Fix: Direct weapon: Don&amp;rsquo;t fire when blocked by defense hardpoint Fix: Simplify repairs logic, prevent &amp;ldquo;stuck&amp;rdquo; repair stations Fix: Hotkey doesn&amp;rsquo;t count selected units correctly Fix: Do not form alliances with scavengers when starting games Fix: Chat message is sent upon clicking anywhere outside of chat widget Fix: Fix the balance of FastPlay since the merging of camBalance Fix: When starting Beta / Gamma from the main menu, no longer block extra structure space at the LZ Fix: Fix OpenGL antialiasing only working at 2x Fix: Vulkan device selection when CPU device types (like llvmpipe) are present Fix: Fix longstanding save-related issue where incomplete research topics could disappear Fix: Make Blender .</description></item><item><title>Version 4.2.7 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-7/</guid><description>Following the recent release of 4.2.6, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.2.7 to fix some issues reported by players:
Fix: VTOLs occasionally land to attack Fix: VTOLs may attempt to &amp;ldquo;attack&amp;rdquo; when empty Fix: Optimum range not moving past long range when clicking a target View the full 4.2.5 - 4.2.7 changelog
(For all the changes in 4.2.0, see the Version 4.2.0 release announcement.)
Download Options
For Windows 10+, Warzone 2100 is now available via the Microsoft Store.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.2.6 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-6/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.2.6, a bug-fix and improvement release.
4.2.6 includes all of the changes from 4.2.5, plus a critical bug fix. Here is a summary of the changes since 4.2.4:
Including:
Numerous fixes for crashes, cleanup issues, and memory leaks Add: Arabic translations (huge thanks to: @mt3d !) Fix: Do not make units move unnecessarily when attached to commanders and ordering an attack Fix: Autorepair not working on units waiting to be built inside a factory when the research is completed Fix: Headless spectator performance improvements Campaign improvements:</description></item><item><title>Version 4.2.5 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-5/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.2.5, a bug-fix and improvement release.
Including:
Numerous fixes for crashes, cleanup issues, and memory leaks Add: Arabic translations (huge thanks to: @mt3d !) Fix: Do not make units move unnecessarily when attached to commanders and ordering an attack Fix: Autorepair not working on units waiting to be built inside a factory when the research is completed Fix: Headless spectator performance improvements Campaign improvements:</description></item><item><title>Version 4.2.4 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-4/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.2.4, a bug-fix release.
Including:
Numerous fixes for crashes, cleanup issues, and memory leaks Fix: Prebuilt ally gates not being passable Fix: Cleanup old log files Campaign improvements:
Change: Ignore VTOLs when a campaign enemy group unit can&amp;rsquo;t hit them Change: Better target selections by sorting targets relative to group average coordinate Change: Add a time range to cam3-1 launch / detonate sounds Change: Make the winning requirements for Beta-end more clear Change: Make Gamma 5 a little more hectic on Hard / Insane difficulty Skirmish / Multiplayer improvements:</description></item><item><title>Version 4.2.3 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-3/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.2.3, a bug-fix release.
Including:
Numerous fixes for crashes, cleanup issues, and memory leaks Fix: Unable to demolish structures at full health Fix: Properly remove old QuickSave data when quick-saving Fix: Drop pending structures on first click Fix: Play buzz sound once per interval Fix: Ultimate Scavengers freeze on certain maps View the full 4.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.2.2 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-2/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.2.2, a bug-fix release.
Including:
New: &amp;ldquo;Multiplay Options&amp;rdquo; menu New: Hotkey to &amp;ldquo;Select all land combat units, with health &amp;gt;50%, not assigned to any group&amp;rdquo; New: Add 7-player map &amp;ldquo;Thales&amp;rdquo; Fixes for initializing OpenGL / Vulkan on certain systems Fix: Don&amp;rsquo;t needlessly move Repair Turrets &amp;amp; Builders Fix: Re-ordering construction units to build something shouldn&amp;rsquo;t cancel it Fix: Don&amp;rsquo;t retreat Repair Turrets (RT) to other RT Fix: Don&amp;rsquo;t reset attack range under commander Fix: Ignore rearm order when already rearming Fix: Don&amp;rsquo;t show green overlay when impossible to build next module Fix: Don&amp;rsquo;t show modules in build list when unable to build more buildings of that type Fix: Factory set Hold Position bug Fix: Various savegame / autosave issues Fix: Partial UI soft-lock with certain in-game menus Fix: Remove Command Relay structure requirement for Command Turret research Fix: Toggling debug mode in skirmish as spectator Fix: Ultimate Scavengers building an absurd amount of factories that could cause the game to freeze Numerous fixes for crashes, cleanup issues, and memory leaks And a few multiplayer balance tweaks:</description></item><item><title>Version 4.2.1 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-1/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.2.1, a bug-fix release.
Including:
Replay v2 format (that embeds downloaded maps for easier sharing) Improved replay saving performance / behavior Improved spectator lag / fast-forward behavior A new native fractal value noise generator for use in map scripts A new button to display spectator stats (i.e. specstats) Host: Remember number of spectator slots in multiplayer games Campaign: Tweaks to Alpha 09, Alpha 06 NP reinforcements Fix: Account for the transporter in campaign unit limit Fix: Do not reset ready status of players on spectator leave Numerous fixes for crashes, cleanup issues, and memory leaks And a number of multiplayer balance tweaks:</description></item><item><title>Version 4.2.0 - The Spectre Update</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-0/</guid><description>With 340 commits since the last release, it’s time for Warzone 2100 v4.2.0!
This release includes Spectators, Replays, Ultimate Scavengers, numerous fixes for multiplayer / skirmish balance, and more!
4.2.0 General Highlights: Add Ultimate Scavengers to the game Spectators for multiplayer games Recorded replays for skirmish / multiplayer Headless / autohost enhancements, spectator stats, lobby chat slash commands Return units to mobile turrets &amp;amp; better distribute around multiple repair points Update camBalance for Gamma (Campaign rebalance is basically complete) Increase oil drum power in Campaign Beta (150) and Gamma (200) Add new random maps &amp;ldquo;DustyMaze&amp;rdquo;: one 2-player and two 4-player maps Use a stable config directory for release builds Implement remove from group shortcut Make selected structures and units blink on radar Add &amp;ldquo;power per second&amp;rdquo; to powerbar tooltip Major revision to the Blender 2.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.2.0-beta2 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-0-beta2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-0-beta2/</guid><description>The second beta release of 4.2.0, 4.2.0-beta2, is available for testing! Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.2.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.2.0-beta2 from SourceForge Download 4.2.0-beta2 from GitHub Releases 4.2.0 beta2 Highlights: Many bug &amp;amp; crash fixes (see full changelog) New: Make selected structures and units blink on radar New: Add &amp;ldquo;power per second&amp;rdquo; to powerbar tooltip The WZ Guide / &amp;ldquo;Betaguide&amp;rdquo; is now also updated for 4.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.2.0-beta1 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-0-beta1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-2-0-beta1/</guid><description>The first beta release of 4.2.0, 4.2.0-beta1, is available for testing! Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.2.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.2.0-beta1 from SourceForge Download 4.2.0-beta1 from GitHub Releases 4.2.0 beta1 Highlights: Add Ultimate Scavengers to the game Spectator slots for multiplayer games Replay functionality for skirmish / multiplayer Headless / autohost enhancements, spectator stats, lobby chat slash commands Return units to mobile turrets &amp;amp; better distribute around multiple repair points Update camBalance for Gamma (Campaign rebalance is basically complete) Add new random maps &amp;ldquo;DustyMaze&amp;rdquo;: one 2-player and two 4-player maps Use a stable config directory for release builds Implement remove from group shortcut Major revision to the Blender 2.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.1.3 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-1-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-1-3/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.1.3, a bug-fix release.
Including:
Numerous fixes for crashes, cleanup issues, and memory leaks Fix: Potential crash affecting campaign level change Fix: Order of players in alliances screen And the following multiplayer balance adjustments:
Reconstruct Howitzer branch and adjust artillery parameters (PR #2070) Make Mantis more accessible (PR #2095) Earlier access to Assault Gun, improve MG (PR #2094) View the full 4.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.1.2 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-1-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-1-2/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.1.2, a bug-fix release.
Including:
Numerous fixes for crashes, cleanup issues, and memory leaks Map request logic improvements Reduction of log-spam Fix: Do not deselect droids when pressing RMB over something Fix: Do not play audio from assignments to commanders from other players Fix: When editing keymappings, ESC should unhighlight the selection Fix: Add new Twin MG Tower to transitionTech.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.1.1 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-1-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-1-1/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.1.1, a bug-fix release.
Including fixes for:
Respecting Hold &amp;amp; Fire At Will better Structure limits screen lighting Using faction models for UI buttons Chat cursor position Beta campaign balance tweaks Compilation / compatibility issues And a number of balance tweaks:
Make Heavy Plasma Launcher more useful with an &amp;ldquo;all rounder&amp;rdquo; role and reduce price of Plasma Cannon significantly (PR #2009) Tweak mortar research paths to decouple Bombard / Pepperpot from damage / ROF upgrades and Incendiary Mortar and reduce Pepperpot weight (PR #2021) Rebalance HVC and HVC Cyborg to have more ROF and 1 tile less range (PR #2022) Tweak accuracy and splash values on Sunburst and Cyclone anti-air weapons (PR #2032) View the full 4.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.1.0 - The Big Balance Update</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-1-0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-1-0/</guid><description>With 380 commits since the last release, it’s time for Warzone 2100 v4.1.0!
This release includes approximately 3 years of work on campaign balance &amp;amp; fixes (the &amp;ldquo;camBalance&amp;rdquo; mod), as well as numerous fixes for multiplayer balance.
Beware: &amp;ldquo;Insane&amp;rdquo; campaign difficulty should now be a challenge for even the most experienced of players. (New players should stick with a lower difficulty level.)
4.1.0 General Highlights: Merge of the &amp;ldquo;camBalance&amp;rdquo; mod that revamps campaign balance and fixes numerous issues Numerous multiplayer balance tweaks (see full changelog for details) Fix fog, add an option to toggle it on New design menu stats delta display Add a single player quit confirmation screen Allow building modules/derricks in a row (with drag &amp;amp; build) Add support for binding same keys to multiple actions in non-conflicting contexts Allow assigning key bindings to mouse keys Add &amp;ldquo;selection without group&amp;rdquo; hotkeys Move the whole group to the target location, not only the command droid New cheat makemehero makes selected units hero rank General improvements to Cobra AI / accounts for new balance changes Fix: Muzzle flash effects for Gauss, laser, and all kinds of weapons Fix: Several crash &amp;amp; UI soft-lock issues Fix: Various save-loading issues Fix: Do not handle RMB click while panning the camera Fix: Unclosable panels and flicker when using the Intelligence map and Design menus Fix: Heavy CPU usage on the Intelligence map Fix: VTOL collision with ground units Fix: Normalmapping of 3D models in menus / buttons Many other bug fixes View the full 4.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.1.0-beta1 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-1-0-beta1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-1-0-beta1/</guid><description>The first beta release of 4.1.0, 4.1.0-beta1, is available for testing! Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.1.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.1.0-beta1 from SourceForge Download 4.1.0-beta1 from GitHub Releases 4.1.0 beta1 Highlights: Fix fog, add an option to toggle it on Merge of the &amp;ldquo;camBalance&amp;rdquo; mod that revamps campaign balance and fixes numerous issues Numerous multiplayer balance tweaks (see full changelog for details) New design menu stats delta display Add a single player quit confirmation screen Allow building modules/derricks in a row (with drag &amp;amp; build) Add support for binding same keys to multiple actions in non-conflicting contexts Allow assigning key bindings to mouse keys Add &amp;ldquo;selection without group&amp;rdquo; hotkeys Move the whole group to the target location, not only the command droid New cheat makemehero makes selected units hero rank Fix: Several crash &amp;amp; UI soft-lock issues Fix: Various save-loading issues Fix: Do not handle RMB click while panning the camera Fix: Unclosable panels and flicker when using the Intelligence map and Design menus Many other bug fixes View the full 4.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.0.1 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-1/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 4.0.1, a bug-fix release.
Including fixes for:
Water rendering performance Additional Collective faction textures Broken map zoom cycle Autosave / saveload issues Multiplayer lobby issues Procedurally-generated map player positioning Compilation / compatibility issues ARM64 / Apple Silicon macOS builds Download Options
View the full 4.0.1 changelog
(For all the changes in 4.0.0, see the Version 4.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.0.0 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-0/</guid><description>With over 1000 commits since the last release, it’s time for Warzone 2100 v4.0.0!
4.0.0 General Highlights: New graphics backend support: New support for: Vulkan 1.0+ OpenGL ES 3.0 / 2.0 DirectX (via libANGLE, OpenGL ES -&amp;gt; DirectX) Metal (via MoltenVK, Vulkan -&amp;gt; Metal) In addition to the existing support for: OpenGL 3.0+ Core Profile (default), OpenGL 2.1 Compatibility Profile See the new &amp;ldquo;Graphics Backend&amp;rdquo; option in the Video Options menu.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.0.0-beta3 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-0-beta3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-0-beta3/</guid><description>The third beta release of 4.0.0, 4.0.0-beta3, is available for testing, with many bug fixes since beta1 &amp;amp; beta2. This is a very large release, and contains multiple changes. Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.0.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.0.0-beta3 from SourceForge Download 4.0.0-beta3 from GitHub Releases 4.0.0 General Highlights: New graphics backend support: New support for: Vulkan 1.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.0.0-beta2 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-0-beta2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-0-beta2/</guid><description>The second beta release of 4.0.0, 4.0.0-beta2, is available for testing, with many bug fixes since beta1. This is a very large release, and contains multiple changes. Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.0.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.0.0-beta2 from SourceForge Download 4.0.0-beta2 from GitHub Releases 4.0.0 General Highlights: New graphics backend support: New support for: Vulkan 1.0+ OpenGL ES 3.</description></item><item><title>Version 4.0.0-beta1 available</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-0-beta1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-4-0-0-beta1/</guid><description>The first beta release of 4.0.0, 4.0.0-beta1, is available for testing! This is a very large release, and contains multiple changes. Please test it intensively so that we may soon push out the final 4.0.0.
It is available at the usual locations:
Download 4.0.0-beta1 from SourceForge Download 4.0.0-beta1 from GitHub Releases 4.0.0 beta1 Highlights: New graphics backend support: New support for: Vulkan 1.0+ OpenGL ES 3.0 / 2.0 DirectX (via libANGLE, OpenGL ES -&amp;gt; DirectX) Metal (via MoltenVK, Vulkan -&amp;gt; Metal) In addition to the existing support for: OpenGL 3.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.4.1 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-3-4-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-3-4-1/</guid><description>With the help of many bug reporters &amp;amp; contributors, we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the release of 3.4.1, a bug-fix release.
Including fixes for:
UI issues Keymap defaults Simple keybinds not firing when a meta key is held down Campaign bugs Compilation / compatibility issues Multiplayer lobby issues View the full 3.4.1 changelog
(For all the changes since 3.3.0, see the Version 3.4.0 release announcement.)
There have been over 70 commits since 3.</description></item><item><title>Version 3.4.0 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-3-4-0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-3-4-0/</guid><description>With over 485 commits since the last release, it&amp;rsquo;s time for 3.4.0!
3.4.0 Highlights: Graphics and UI improvements, including: fade effect when starting games, smoother mouse rotation, smoother zooming, interpolate frames in animation, occlude terrain ambiently Add: Frontend &amp;ldquo;continue last save&amp;rdquo; option Add: Quicksave feature Add: Autosave feature Add: Way to change most game settings with the in-game pause menu Add: Shortcut to quit to main-menu after victory Add: T4 technology level where all research is completed Add: Randomization of game options button in skirmish/multiplayer games Add: Add support for changing map, game name, and hosting player&amp;rsquo;s name after already hosting Add: Configuration of OpenAL-HRTF mode Add: In-game notification widgets Add: Keybinding configuration for camera pan Add: Discord rich presence / join support Add: Unit / kill count gui feature Add: BoneCrusher!</description></item><item><title>Version 3.3.0 released</title><link>https://wz2100.net/news/version-3-3-0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wz2100.net/news/version-3-3-0/</guid><description>It has been three years since the last stable release. There is an enormous amount of changes in this release compared to 3.2.0. These changes include:
Display / UI scaling Performance improvements Major improvements to campaign The return of secondary orders removed in the previous release Fix for shooting through walls The return of macOS builds and many, many other things Below you can see the list of changes compared to the previous beta release: View the full 3.</description></item></channel></rss>